<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="DNA_SESSION_TIMEOUT_MESSAGE">Your session has been timed out.</string>
    <string name="DNA_ERROR_GENERIC_ERROR_MESSAGE">Something went wrong please try again</string>
    <string name="DNA_ERROR_INVALID_CONTEXT_MESSAGE">Context is invalid</string>
    <string name="DNA_ERROR_ARCHITECTURE_NOT_SUPPORTED_MESSAGE">Device architecture not supported</string>

    <string name="DNA_LDA_HEADER_SET_FINGERPRINT_NAME">Enable Biometric Access</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_HEADER_VERIFY_FINGERPRINT_NAME">Please Authenticate</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_HELP">BiometricAuthenticationHelp</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_FAILED">BiometricAuthenticationFailed</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_ERROR">BiometricAuthenticationError</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_SUCCESS">BiometricAuthenticationSuccess</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_CANCELLED">BiometricAuthenticationCancelled</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_NOT_AVAILABLE">BiometricAuthenticationNotAvailable</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_NOT_SUPPORTED">BiometricAuthenticationNotSupported</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_INTERNAL_ERROR">BiometricAuthenticationInternalError</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_AUTHENTICATION_PERMISSION_NOT_GRANTED">BiometricAuthenticationPermissionNotGranted</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_TITLE_NULL_ERROR">Biometric Dialog title cannot be null</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_SUBTITLE_NULL_ERROR">Biometric Dialog subtitle cannot be null</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_DESCRIPTION_NULL_ERROR">Biometric Dialog description cannot be null</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_BUTTON_NULL_ERROR">Biometric Dialog negative button text cannot be null</string>
    <string name="DNA_BIOMETRIC_DEFAULT_TITLE">Enable authentication</string>
    <string name="DNA_BIOMETRIC_DEFAULT_SUBTITLE"></string>
    <string name="DNA_BIOMETRIC_DEFAULT_DESCRIPTION"></string>
    <string name="DNA_BIOMETRIC_SUCCESS_MESSAGE">Authentication Successful.</string>

    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_HEADER_NAME">Set Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_CONFIRM_HEADER_NAME">Provide Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_UPDATE_HEADER_NAME">Provide Current Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_UPDATE_HEADER_SET_NAME">Set New Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_LOGIN_CONFIRM_HEADER_NAME">Confirm Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_UPDATE_HEADER_CONFIRM_NAME">Confirm Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_AUTHENTICATION_FAILED">PatternAuthenticationFailed</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_AUTHENTICATION_SUCCESS">PatternAuthenticationSuccess</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_AUTHENTICATION_CANCELLED">PatternAuthenticationCancelled</string>

    <string name="DNA_LDA_USER_NAME">DNA_LDA_USER_NAME</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_DESCRIPTION">DNA_LDA_DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_CANCEL_BUTTON">Cancel</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_ENABLE_MESSAGE_KEY">LDA_ENABLE_MSG</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_VERIFY_MESSAGE_KEY">LDA_VERIFY_MSG</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_SUB_HEADER_NAME">Please verify your identity</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_NEW_LINE_MESSAGE_KEY">\n</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_STEPUP_NOTIFICATION_MESSAGE_KEY">LDA_STEPUP_NOTF_MSG</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_SETUP_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Enable authentication for __USER_ID__</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_VERIFY_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Provide authentication for __USER_ID__</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_STEPUP_NOTIFICATION_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Provide authentication for __USER_ID__</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_ENABLE_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Enable Pin/Pattern/Password/Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_VERIFY_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Provide Pin/Pattern/Password/Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_STEP_UP_AUTH_GENERIC_BIO_MESSAGE">Provide Pin/Pattern/Password/Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_ENABLE_BIOMETRIC">Enable Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_VERIFY_BIOMETRIC">Provide Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_MESSAGE_STEP_UP_AUTH_BIOMETRIC">Provide Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_ATTEMPTS_LEFT">Attempts left</string>

    <string name="DNA_LDA_SDK_VERSION_NOT_SUPPORTED">SdkVersionNotSupported</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_BIOMETRIC_MACRO_VALUE">Biometric</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_FACE_MACRO_VALUE">Face recognition</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_REG_MACRO_VALUE">Fingerprint/Face recognition/Pattern</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_DEVICE_LDA_MACRO_VALUE">Local device</string>
    <string name="DNA_LDA_PATTERN_MACRO_VALUE">pattern</string>


    <string name="error_0">Success</string>
    <string name="error_1">SDK not initialized. Initialize the SDK for further activities.</string>
    <string name="error_2">Internal error occurred. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_3">Invalid SDK version.</string>
    <string name="error_4">Invalid arguments provided.</string>
    <string name="error_5">Your session has expired.</string>
    <string name="error_7">Invalid callbacks provided.</string>
    <string name="error_13">Invalid core data found during resume. Re-initialize the application.</string>
    <string name="error_23">An error occurred while initializing SDK. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_24">An internal error occurred while saving the core state during the pause runtime. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_25">An internal error occurred while initiating the core during the resume runtime. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_26">An internal error occurred while terminating the core.</string>
    <string name="error_73">The application ran out of memory. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_74">Invalid core context. Re-initialize the application.</string>
    <string name="error_88">SDK is already initialized.</string>
    <string name="error_96">CORE_ERR_ARCHITECTURE_NOT_SUPPORTED</string>
    <string name="error_97">Invalid device context provide, Please try again by re-launching the application.</string>
    <string name="error_98">SDK cannot be instantiated. Internal Error occurred while the security notification activity. Please contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_103">Conflicting internal arguments provided to SDK. Please contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_179">SDK initialization is already in progress, kindly wait till the process completes and try initializing again if a failure occurs</string>

    <string name="error_6">Failed to connect to the server via a proxy. Kindly check your network settings.</string>
    <string name="error_8">Invalid server Host/IP.</string>
    <string name="error_9">Invalid server port.</string>
    <string name="error_10">Invalid connection settings.</string>
    <string name="error_12">Failed to connect to a server. Kindly check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="error_55">Domain name resolution failed. Kindly contact admin if the issue persists.</string>
    <string name="error_56">No network connection detected. Please check to make sure you are connected to a network to continue.</string>
    <string name="error_57">Timeout occurred while attempting connection. The server may be too busy to accept new connections.</string>
    <string name="error_58">Internal network error occurred.</string>
    <string name="error_62">Unable to connect to the server. The connection attempt timed out, Please check your network settings and try again if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_63">DNS request timed-out. Please check your network settings and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_64">The server failed to respond within the specified time. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_180">Failed to connect to server - server actively refused the connection. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_209">The connection to the server was broken or was forcibly closed by the remote host, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_17">The service you are trying to access is not valid or not configured. Kindly contact admin for further details.</string>
    <string name="error_163">Internal server error occurred. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_164">Access token generation facility is not available at the moment, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_165">Invalid response was received from the server, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_181">Error occurred while processing the request, Please try again after some time. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_14">Failed to parse HTTP requests. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_15">Failed to parse HTTP response. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_16">Invalid cipher specs. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_52">Failed to open rest HTTP service. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_72">Invalid rest HTTP API request URL. Please retry with valid HTTP details.</string>
    <string name="error_86">Failed to deserialize JSON</string>
    <string name="error_87">Invalid challenge JSON received</string>
    <string name="error_193">Unable to process your request, malformed request received. Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin</string>
    <string name="error_194">Unable to process your request, provided HTTP method not supported. Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin</string>
    <string name="error_195">Unable to process your request, unsupported HTTP protocol. Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin</string>

    <string name="error_18">RDNA_ERR_FAILED_TO_GET_STREAM_PRIVACYSCOPE</string>
    <string name="error_19">RDNA_ERR_FAILED_TO_GET_STREAM_TYPE</string>
    <string name="error_20">RDNA_ERR_FAILED_TO_WRITE_INTO_STREAM</string>
    <string name="error_21">RDNA_ERR_FAILED_TO_END_STREAM</string>
    <string name="error_22">RDNA_ERR_FAILED_TO_DESTROY_STREAM</string>
    <string name="error_39">Error occurred while creating privacy stream. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_53">Error occurred while initializing the security certificates provided. Kindly contact admin if the issue persists.</string>
    <string name="error_54">Internal error occurred. There seems to be an issue with the security certificates provided.</string>
    <string name="error_66">An error occurred while securing your connection. Kindly correct your system date and time and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_27">Failed to get cipher salt. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_28">Failed to get cipher specs. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_29">Failed to get Agent ID. Kindly reinitialize the application and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_30">Failed to get session ID. Kindly reinitialize the application and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_31">Failed to get device ID. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_35">An error occurred while using data at rest API while encrypting data. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_36">An error occurred while using data at rest API while decrypting data. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_37">An error occurred while using data at rest API while encrypting HTTP request. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_38">An error occurred while using data at rest API while decrypting HTTP response. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_59">Invalid user state in secure storage. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_61">Invalid proxy credentials provided. Please provide valid credentials and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_75">Invalid input length specified for decryption, Please try again with a valid value. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_76">Invalid input provided for decryption, Please try again with valid input. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_77">Invalid input provided for encryption, Please try again with valid input. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_78">Invalid input length specified for encryption, Please try again with a valid value. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_79">Invalid user ID provided. Please retry with a valid user ID.</string>
    <string name="error_102">User saved state corrupted or was cleared from this device. Please re-activate yourself on this device. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_158">Invalid credential provided. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_177">Failed to recover Login-ID, invalid E-Mail ID provided. Please try again with a valid E-MAIL ID. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_178">Invalid Login ID provided</string>

    <string name="error_11">Invalid agent REL-ID was found in the connection profile. Kindly contact admin for further details.</string>
    <string name="error_32">Failed to get service details. Kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_33">Failed to start service. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_34">Failed to stop service. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_65">An unsupported user REL-ID found. Kindly contact admin for further details.</string>
    <string name="error_70">Failed to parse device details.</string>
    <string name="error_84">Invalid or empty service name provided, Please retry with the valid service name.</string>
    <string name="error_85">Invalid device details provided for updation, Please retry with valid details.</string>
    <string name="error_148">This device has been blocked by admin.</string>
    <string name="error_149">Session can\'t be created as the user is already logged in from another device.</string>
    <string name="error_162">Unable to activate the device - Device limit exceeded. Kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_216">Login-id and username cannot be the same. Kindly enter a new login-id.</string>
    <string name="error_210">The server encountered an internal error while adding specified LOGIN-ID, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_211">You have insufficient privileges to perform this task, please try again with another user, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_40">An internal error occurred while performing a challenge request response. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_41">An internal error occurred while performing an update credentials request. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_42">An internal error occurred while fetching application configuration from the server. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_43">Failed to get all configured updated challenges. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_45">An error occurred while resetting the challenges. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_47">Failed to fetch post login challenges. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_71">Invalid challenge configuration received. Please try again. if the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_80">Invalid challenge response submitted, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_82">Invalid use case specified for post-login authentication, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_107">Invalid challenge authentication sequence. Kindly re-initialize the application and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_108">Invalid authentication details received. Kindly try again.</string>
    <string name="error_116">Unable to proceed with user authentication. Invalid user auth configuration on the server. Please contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_117">Unable to reset user authentication sequence, inconsistent SDK state. Kindly re-launch and initialize the application. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_118">Unable to perform the update operation, No credentials to update.</string>
    <string name="error_119">Un-supported challenge/s configured on the server, Please re-launch the application and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_120">Invalid API executed against the internal state, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_121">Unable to proceed with user activation, Activation choice currently not supported, Please try again with a different activation choice.</string>
    <string name="error_122">Operation cannot be completed, invalid user authentication sequence state. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_123">Update operation cannot be completed as, the credential you are trying to update is not supported for updation. Retry again with other supported credentials.</string>
    <string name="error_124">Unable to activate user, invalid or no supported authentication mechanism registered. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_125">Unable complete user activation. Failed to generate and save user data</string>
    <string name="error_126">Users biometric authentication failed. Cannot activate the user. Please try again. If the issue persists try to activate using other activation options if available or kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_128">Invalid challenge received as part of initial challenge, Kindly try again by re-launching the application. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_129">LOGIN ID already exists. Please try again with a different LOGIN ID.</string>
    <string name="error_130">An error occurred while adding LOGIN ID. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_140">Password policy validation failed, invalid policy configuration, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_141">Provided password does not satisfy the password policy set.</string>
    <string name="error_142">You have exceeded the limit to set login id. Please contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_147">Credential update failed, Entered current credentials do not match login credentials, you will be logged off kindly retry after logging in.</string>
    <string name="error_150">Attempts exhausted while enabling additional authentications. For security reasons you will be logged out of the application.</string>
    <string name="error_153">The requested authentication mechanism is already in the desired state, nothing to update.</string>
    <string name="error_155">Authentication mechanism is currently not supported. Please try again with a different mechanism. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_156">Unable to proceed with the request, failed to start the authorization process. kindly re-login and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_159">Unable to proceed with the requested authentication mechanism. Please try again with a different mechanism. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_167">Current and new password should be different</string>
    <string name="error_171">Current and new patterns should be different</string>
    <string name="error_182">Unable to process your request, the attempts limit has not been properly configured. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_213">Request failed. The additional authentication is already in progress please wait for it to complete and try again. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_214">Request failed. Specified additional authentication is not supported, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_403">A change in device authentication settings have been detected, unable to proceed with your request at the moment, Kindly re-enable authentication settings from the menu and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_407">The chosen verification option is not supported, please try again with a valid verification method</string>
    <string name="error_413">The selected authentication method is not supported at this time. Please choose a different method. If the issue persists, contact your administrator for assistance.</string>

    <string name="error_44">An error occurred while logging off the user. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_46">Failed to perform forgot password. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_48">Failed to get registered user device details. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_49">Failed to update user device details. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_60">Failure occurred when signing notification. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_67">User session is invalid. Failed to fetch notification history.</string>
    <string name="error_68">An error occurred while fetching notification history. Please try again or Kindly contact admin if the issue persists.</string>
    <string name="error_69">Invalid tunnel configurations received. Please try again. if the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_81">Internal error occurred while serializing data, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_83">Invalid notification history payload received, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_143">Your session has been terminated - User REL-ID not found. Kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_152">You need to login into the application to use this feature.</string>
    <string name="error_154">Operation you wish to perform cannot be completed due to an internal error, kindly re-login and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_157">Unable to perform operation due to incomplete data, Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_161">Your session is terminated - User or Device state is invalid. Kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_166">You are not logged in. Kindly login with a valid username and credentials and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_414">You have been logged out due to security reasons.Kindly login to activate your device.</string>

    <string name="error_50">Failed to get the notification for the user. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_51">Failed to update user\'s action performed on a notification. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_131">Failed to update notification, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_132">Failed to update notification, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_133">Failed to update notification, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_134">Failed to update notification, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_135">Failed to update notification, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_136">Failed to update notification, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_137">Failed to update notification, Pattern authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_138">Failed to update notification, authentication failure</string>
    <string name="error_205">Failed to update notification, configured authentication is not supported, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_206">Failed to update notification, the required additional authentication is already in progress please wait for it to complete and try again. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_207">Unable to process your request, maximum attempts for additional authentication exhausted, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_89">__FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_90">__FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_91">__FINGERPRINT__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_92">__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_93">__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_94">__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_95">Pattern authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_99">Kindly enable/register __FINGERPRINT__ authentication from device settings and retry again.</string>
    <string name="error_100">Kindly enable/register __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication from device settings and retry again.</string>
    <string name="error_101">Pattern authentication not supported. Please try again. If the issues persist, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_139">You need to enable __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication from the device settings and authorize yourself to respond to a notification.</string>
    <string name="error_160">An attempt to activate local device authentication (__LDA__) was skipped or failed. You can activate this from settings at a later point in time.</string>
    <string name="error_168">We have sensed a change in the existing __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication settings which can access your phone. As a security measure, you will be asked to re-activate your device.</string>
    <string name="error_169">Your session has been terminated - __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication which is used to access your phone has been modified.</string>
    <string name="error_184">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_185">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_186">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FINGERPRINT__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_187">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_188">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by the system</string>
    <string name="error_189">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, __FACERECOGNITION__ authentication operation was cancelled because the API is locked out due to too many attempts. Try again after some time.</string>
    <string name="error_190">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity, Pattern authentication cancelled by user</string>
    <string name="error_191">Request failed. User authentication failure</string>
    <string name="error_192">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity. You need to enable __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication from the device settings and authorize yourself to proceed.</string>
    <string name="error_196">__FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication cancelled by application, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_197">Unable to process __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication due to invalid context, Please try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_198">__FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication attempt with an apple watch was unsuccessful as the system could not locate a nearby paired apple watch running</string>
    <string name="error_199">Unable to process __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication as displaying the required authentication user interface is forbidden. Please try again. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_200">Internal error occurred while performing __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication.</string>
    <string name="error_201">Request failed. No fallback option is available for __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication, Please try again. If the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_202">Passcode isn\'t set on the device, Kindly set a valid passcode from system settings and try again, if the issue persists kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_203">__FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication not supported.</string>
    <string name="error_204">__FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication was unsuccessful as the necessary authentication settings were not enabled in the device settings.</string>
    <string name="error_217">You have declined permission to use __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication.</string>
    <string name="error_404">You need to enable atleast one __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication from the device settings and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_405">Please provide your password to proceed as we have found that no __FINGERPRINT__/__FACERECOGNITION__ authentication settings are enabled on the device.</string>
    <string name="error_406">Palm Vein identification not supported or not available at this time, please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_104">Invalid TOTP context object received. Kindly re-initialize the application and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_105">Invalid TOTP configuration received from the server. Kindly log in again to enable TOTP. If the issue persists, contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_106">User successfully registered for TOTP.</string>
    <string name="error_109">Authentication cancelled by User while generating TOTP.</string>
    <string name="error_110">User is not registered for TOTP. Kindly log in to enable TOTP.</string>
    <string name="error_111">Request received to generate TOTP for a user other than the LOGGED-IN user.</string>
    <string name="error_112">TOTP will be generated only if the user is either OFFLINE or successfully LOGGED-IN.</string>
    <string name="error_113">An error occurred in TOTP flows. Kindly try again. If the issue persists, contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_114">User authentication attempts for TOTP exhausted. TOTP generation is blocked for the user. Please login into the application to re-register for TOTP.</string>
    <string name="error_115">An error occurred while registering the user for TOTP. Kindly validate your system date and time and try again. If the issue persists, contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_127">TOTP feature is not supported or enabled for your application. Kindly contact admin</string>
    <string name="error_215">TOTP registration is in progress. Please wait and try after a while.</string>
    <string name="error_219">An error occurred while registering for TOTP, possibly due to a time mismatch between your device and the server. Kindly correct your system date and time to use automatic settings and try to log in again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>

    <string name="error_144">Application integrity is compromised. Kindly re-install the application. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_145">Your device is not secure. Kindly resolve the reported threats and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_170">The feature or operation that you are trying to access is not supported in the current configuration. Please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_172">The application you are using is a debug build. Kindly install the application from a trusted app store and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_173">The application is running on an emulator. Kindly run the application on a physical android device and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_174">The application is not installed from a trusted source. Kindly install the application from a trusted app store and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_175">Package information of this application is invalid. Kindly contact admin for more details.</string>
    <string name="error_176">The application is repackaged and is not safe to use. Kindly install the application from a trusted app store and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_208">Your device may be insecure, threat scan was not successful, missing app insight key in MTD configuration, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_218">Your device is not secure. Kindly resolve the reported threats and try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>
    <string name="error_401">The operation performed is invalid, only Mobile Threat Detection features are enabled</string>
    <string name="error_412">We\'re sorry, but your device lacks the necessary built-in security features required to protect your account. For your safety, access is not permitted on this device. Please try using a different device with enhanced security capabilities.</string>
    <string name="error_415">The version of the app you\'re using is no longer supported. Please update to the latest version to continue using all features and ensure security.</string>

    <string name="error_146">Your identity verification process failed.</string>
    <string name="error_212">Failed to perform KYC operation, user ID provided should be different than logged-in user ID</string>
    <string name="error_220">IDV core library not found.</string>
    <string name="error_221">IDV document scan library not found.</string>
    <string name="error_222">IDV selfie capture library not found.</string>
    <string name="error_223">Null or invalid context received for IDV core.</string>
    <string name="error_224">Null or invalid context received for IDV selfie capture.</string>
    <string name="error_225">Null or invalid context received for IDV document capture.</string>
    <string name="error_226">Internal error occurred during IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_227">Invalid challenge received during IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_228">Invalid challenge operation mode received for IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_229">Invalid IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_230">Invalid usecase name received for IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_231">Invalid transaction ID received for IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_232">Invalid User ID received for IDV workflow.</string>
    <string name="error_233">KYC process failed due to invalid user ID.</string>
    <string name="error_234">IDV activation was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_235">IDV activation with template canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_236">IDV additional device activation was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_237">IDV additional device activation without template canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_238">IDV account recovery with template canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_239">IDV account recovery without template canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_240">IDV post login KYC canceled by the user</string>
    <string name="error_241">IDV additional document scan canceled by the user</string>
    <string name="error_242">IDV selfie biometric was canceled by the user</string>
    <string name="error_243">IDV step - up authentication was canceled by the user</string>
    <string name="error_244">IDV opt - in was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_245">IDV opt - out was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_246">IDV KYC for user canceled by the agent.</string>
    <string name="error_247">IDV onboarding was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_248">IDV login flow was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_249">IDV setup authentication and sign data flow were canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_250">Invalid app configuration provided for IDV.</string>
    <string name="error_251">Invalid document scan configuration provided.</string>
    <string name="error_252">Invalid selfie capture configuration provided.</string>
    <string name="error_253">Camera permission is not provided by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_254">File read - write permission is not provided by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_255">Invalid PKD certificate URL provided.</string>
    <string name="error_256">PKD certificate not found.</string>
    <string name="error_257">Failed to download the PKD certificate.</string>
    <string name="error_258">Invalid database url provided.</string>
    <string name="error_259">Document scan database not found.</string>
    <string name="error_260">Failed to download the database.</string>
    <string name="error_261">Document scan license not found.</string>
    <string name="error_262">Invalid arguments provided.</string>
    <string name="error_263">Internal error occurred during KYC flow.</string>
    <string name="error_264">The selfie capture flow was canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_265">Insufficient storage.</string>
    <string name="error_266">Invalid audit info provided.</string>
    <string name="error_267">Failed to record the transaction details for IDV.</string>
    <string name="error_268">Null or invalid callback object received for IDV core.</string>
    <string name="error_269">Null or invalid callback object received for IDV selfie capture.</string>
    <string name="error_270">Null or invalid callback object received for IDV document capture.</string>
    <string name="error_271">IDV asset loading error occurred during Selfie capture initialization.</string>
    <string name="error_272">IDV Selfie capture license expired.</string>
    <string name="error_273">IDV profile could not be loaded during Selfie capture initialization.</string>
    <string name="error_274">IDV internal init error occurred during Selfie capture initialization.</string>
    <string name="error_275">IDV model initialization error occurred during selfie capture init.</string>
    <string name="error_276">IDV Selfie capture canceled by selfie SDK.</string>
    <string name="error_277">IDV SDK failed to create a window.</string>
    <string name="error_278">IDV SDK failed to create a root view controller.</string>
    <string name="error_279">IDV Document scan license data is nil or invalid.</string>
    <string name="error_280">IDV Document scan callback registration failed.</string>
    <string name="error_281">Unknown exception occurred at the document scan layer.</string>
    <string name="error_282">Unknown exception occurred at the document reader state.</string>
    <string name="error_283">Wrong input was provided for IDV document capture.</string>
    <string name="error_284">IDV document scanner initialization failed.</string>
    <string name="error_285">The wrong input was provided for IDV online processing.</string>
    <string name="error_286">IDV license file is absent or corrupted.</string>
    <string name="error_287">The IDV license may be expired, or the date and time set on the device don\'t correspond to reality.</string>
    <string name="error_288">IDV invalid license version.</string>
    <string name="error_289">IDV invalid device ID for the license.</string>
    <string name="error_290">An invalid app package name is detected for IDV.</string>
    <string name="error_291">There are no capabilities for this functionality in your IDV license.</string>
    <string name="error_292">There are no authenticity capabilities in your IDV license.</string>
    <string name="error_293">Incorrect or corrupted database file for IDV.</string>
    <string name="error_294">IDV Bluetooth LE error.</string>
    <string name="error_295">The application was in the background during the document scan.</string>
    <string name="error_296">IDV SDK database error during download or is corrupted.</string>
    <string name="error_297">Failed to set TCC parameters for IDV.</string>
    <string name="error_298">IDV failed during the online processing.</string>
    <string name="error_299">Bluetooth LE feature is not supported on your device during IDV operation.</string>
    <string name="error_300">IDV Document scan canceled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_301">IDV Document scan error occurred during the completion handling.</string>
    <string name="error_302">IDV Document scan error occurred during result parsing.</string>
    <string name="error_303">The scanned document type is invalid.</string>
    <string name="error_304">Failed to extract the document detail, Field Types are empty.</string>
    <string name="error_305">The scanned document is not supported.</string>
    <string name="error_306">Failed to initialize the RFID scan session.</string>
    <string name="error_307">IDV error occurred during the RFID scan completion.</string>
    <string name="error_308">Document Reader Core framework is absent.</string>
    <string name="error_309">This scenario is not supported based on your license and Core framework capabilities.</string>
    <string name="error_310">There are no results after the recognition of camera frames.</string>
    <string name="error_311">An error is encountered during database removal.</string>
    <string name="error_312">An error is encountered to fetch the database.</string>
    <string name="error_313">IDV error incorrect database ID.</string>
    <string name="error_314">IDV error Database description not found.</string>
    <string name="error_315">IDV error is encountered to save the database on your device.</string>
    <string name="error_316">IDV database is corrupted or checksum is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="error_317">IDV eror failed to create database.</string>
    <string name="error_318">IDV RFID Internal error occurred.</string>
    <string name="error_319">IDV Incorrect Database ID provided.</string>
    <string name="error_320">IDV Invalid database config received.</string>
    <string name="error_321">IDV database download is in progress.</string>
    <string name="error_322">IDV document scan database is not selected.</string>
    <string name="error_323">IDV internal client error.</string>
    <string name="error_324">IDV internal document scan SDK error.</string>
    <string name="error_325">IDV selfie capture failed.</string>
    <string name="error_326">IDV document scan license online error.</string>
    <string name="error_327">IDV error no database available.</string>
    <string name="error_328">IDV error incorrect database provided.</string>
    <string name="error_329">IDV error occurred during the RFID scan inprogress.</string>
    <string name="error_330">IDV passive authentication certificate not found.</string>
    <string name="error_331">IDV error response json conversion failed</string>
    <string name="error_332">IDV palm verification canceled by user.</string>
    <string name="error_333">IDV customer detail saved successfully.</string>
    <string name="error_334">Person onboarding canceled by agent</string>
    <string name="error_335">IDV palm Enrollment canceled by user.</string>
    <string name="error_336">IDV PALM capture library not found.</string>
    <string name="error_337">IDV error failed to log event</string>
    <string name="error_338">Your identity verification process failed Err - 338.</string>
    <string name="error_339">Your identity verification process failed Err - 339.</string>
    <string name="error_340">Your identity verification process failed Err - 340.</string>
    <string name="error_341">Your identity verification process failed Err - 341.</string>
    <string name="error_342">Your identity verification process failed Err - 342.</string>
    <string name="error_343">Your identity verification process failed Err - 343.</string>
    <string name="error_344">Your identity verification process failed Err - 344.</string>
    <string name="error_345">Your identity verification process failed Err - 345.</string>
    <string name="error_346">Your identity verification process failed Err - 346.</string>
    <string name="error_347">Your identity verification process failed Err - 347.</string>
    <string name="error_348">Your identity verification process failed Err - 348.</string>
    <string name="error_349">Your identity verification process failed Err - 349.</string>
    <string name="error_350">Your identity verification process failed Err - 350.</string>
    <string name="error_351">Your identity verification process failed Err - 351.</string>
    <string name="error_352">Your identity verification process failed Err - 352.</string>
    <string name="error_353">Your identity verification process failed Err - 353.</string>
    <string name="error_354">Your identity verification process failed Err - 354.</string>
    <string name="error_355">Your identity verification process failed Err - 355.</string>
    <string name="error_356">Your identity verification process failed Err - 356.</string>
    <string name="error_357">Your identity verification process failed Err - 357.</string>
    <string name="error_358">Your identity verification process failed Err - 358.</string>
    <string name="error_359">Your identity verification process failed Err - 359.</string>
    <string name="error_360">Your identity verification process failed Err - 360.</string>
    <string name="error_361">Your identity verification process failed Err - 361.</string>
    <string name="error_362">Your identity verification process failed Err - 362.</string>
    <string name="error_363">Your identity verification process failed Err - 363.</string>
    <string name="error_364">Your identity verification process failed Err - 364.</string>
    <string name="error_365">Your identity verification process failed Err - 365.</string>
    <string name="error_366">Your identity verification process failed Err - 366.</string>
    <string name="error_367">Your identity verification process failed Err - 367.</string>
    <string name="error_368">Your identity verification process failed Err - 368.</string>
    <string name="error_369">Your identity verification process failed Err - 369.</string>
    <string name="error_370">Your identity verification process failed Err - 370.</string>
    <string name="error_371">Your identity verification process failed Err - 371.</string>
    <string name="error_372">Your identity verification process failed Err - 372.</string>
    <string name="error_373">Your identity verification process failed Err - 373.</string>
    <string name="error_374">Your identity verification process failed Err - 374.</string>
    <string name="error_375">Your identity verification process failed Err - 375.</string>
    <string name="error_376">Your identity verification process failed Err - 376.</string>
    <string name="error_377">Your identity verification process failed Err - 377.</string>
    <string name="error_378">Your identity verification process failed Err - 378.</string>
    <string name="error_379">Your identity verification process failed Err - 379.</string>
    <string name="error_380">Your identity verification process failed Err - 380.</string>
    <string name="error_381">Your identity verification process failed Err - 381.</string>
    <string name="error_382">Your identity verification process failed Err - 382.</string>
    <string name="error_383">Your identity verification process failed Err - 383.</string>
    <string name="error_384">Your identity verification process failed Err - 384.</string>
    <string name="error_385">Your identity verification process failed Err - 385.</string>
    <string name="error_386">Your identity verification process failed Err - 386.</string>
    <string name="error_387">Your identity verification process failed Err - 387.</string>
    <string name="error_388">Your identity verification process failed Err - 388.</string>
    <string name="error_389">Your identity verification process failed Err - 389.</string>
    <string name="error_390">Your identity verification process failed Err - 390.</string>
    <string name="error_391">Your identity verification process failed Err - 391.</string>
    <string name="error_392">Your identity verification process failed Err - 392.</string>
    <string name="error_393">Your identity verification process failed Err - 393.</string>
    <string name="error_394">Your identity verification process failed Err - 394.</string>
    <string name="error_395">Your identity verification process failed Err - 395.</string>
    <string name="error_396">Your identity verification process failed Err - 396.</string>
    <string name="error_397">Your identity verification process failed Err - 397.</string>
    <string name="error_398">Your identity verification process failed Err - 398.</string>
    <string name="error_399">Your identity verification process failed Err - 399.</string>
    <string name="error_400">Your identity verification process failed Err - 400.</string>
    <string name="error_408">Digital identity workflow aborted successfully.</string>
    <string name="error_409">Currently there is no worklfow in progress, kindly initiate a worklfow to proceed with the operation</string>
    <string name="error_410">Your account recovery was successful! For your security, please log in again to continue.</string>
    <string name="error_411">Your credential has been successfully updated! For your security, please log in again.</string>

    <string name="error_416">SIM Binding failed due to an invalid server configuration. Please re-launch and initialize the application. If the issue continues, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_417">SIM Binding request failed: OTP validation attempts exhausted. Please re-initiate the process. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_418">An internal error occurred while generating the OTP. Please re-initiate the process. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_419">An internal error occurred during OTP validation. Please re-initiate the process. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_420">SIM Binding request failed due to an internal error. Please try again. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_421">SIM Binding process was cancelled by the user.</string>
    <string name="error_422">SIM Binding failed: SMS operation timed out.</string>
    <string name="error_423">SIM Binding request failed: Required permissions were not granted. Please enable permissions and try again. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_424">SIM Binding request failed: No network detected. Please ensure your phone has an active network connection and Airplane mode is turned off. Then try again. If the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_425">SIM Binding request failed: This device does not support cellular connectivity. Please use a device with an active SIM and mobile network support.</string>
    <string name="error_426">SIM Binding failed: This device lacks the required built-in security features needed to securely bind your SIM. For your protection, this operation is not permitted on this device. Please try again using a device with hardware-backed security.</string>
    <string name="error_427">Your account recovery was successful. To ensure your security, SIM binding must be re-verified on this device. Please proceed with SIM binding and log in again to continue.</string>
    <string name="error_428">SIM binding request failed. Please check that your SIM is properly inserted or that your eSIM profile is correctly set up. Try again, and if the issue persists, contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_429">Your session has expired as SIM binding registration was detected from another device. Kindly re-register SIM binding to continue using the app.</string>

    <string name="error_183">Request failed. Unable to verify user identity. Please try again. If the issue persists kindly contact admin</string>
    <string name="error_402">Failed to perform operation, invalid input provided, please try again. If the issue persists, kindly contact admin.</string>


</resources>